<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Cats list</string>
    <string name="breed_abyssinian"> The Abyssinian </string>
    <string name="decr_abyssinian">The Abyssinian is a slender, fine-boned, medium-sized cat. The
        head is moderately wedge shaped, with a slight break at the muzzle, and nose and chin
        ideally forming a straight vertical line when viewed in profile. They have alert,
        relatively large pointed ears.  </string>

    <string name="breed_exotic_shorthair"> Exotic Shorthair </string>
    <string name="descr_exotic_shorthair"> Exotic Shorthairs have a gentle and calm personality
        reminiscent of the Persian, but are generally livelier than their longhaired ancestors.
        Curious and playful, they are friendly to other cats and dogs, but they dont like being
        left alone and need the presence of their owner. They tend to show more affection and
        loyalty than most breeds and make excellent lap cats.</string>

    <string name="breed_the_korat">The Korat</string>
    <string name="descr_the_korat">The Korats unusual colour is actually a silver-tipped blue that
        appears to shimmer. The Thais refer to this colour as rain-cloud grey, and the shimmer as
        sea foam. This cat has a single coat that is short, with roots of a lighter silver blue.
        The hair shaft colour increases to deeper blue and the tips are silver, especially on the
        muzzle and toes. This is the only colour accepted for a Korat.</string>

    <string name="breed_ocicat">Ocicat</string>
    <string name="descr_ocicat">The devoted and playful Ocicat loves people and will trail their
        footsteps through the house or ride on a shoulder. Guests are welcomed by this generally
        social cat as new opportunities for petting or lap sitting. Ocicats don’t even mind being
        carried around as long as they are with you. As with any animal, they come in a range of
        personalities, so some are more shy than others. Favorite activities include retrieving
        toys and learning to walk on a leash. Ocicats are highly intelligent and learn tricks easily.
    </string>

    <string name="breed_laPerm">LaPerm</string>
    <string name="descr_laPerm">The clever LaPerm has a sense of humor. Often described as clownish,
        he is something of a mischief-maker who makes talented use of his paws to open doors, swipe
        things he wants or tap you on the shoulder for attention. He’s not clingy, but he likes to
        be with you and will follow you around, sit on your shoulder or the top of your computer,
        or sit in your lap, whichever option is most convenient for him. He is moderately active
        and enjoys retrieving items that are thrown for him.
    </string>

    <string name="breed_russian_white">Russian White</string>
    <string name="descr_russian_white">Russian White Cats are a medium sized breed of domestic cats.
        Russian white cats are delicate and elegant cat and have been a woman’s classy cat since
        decades. Russian White cats were bred in the 1970’s from Russian Blue Cats. These cats live
        a long life of 15 years. These cats are available in white, black and chocolate color.
    </string>

    <string name="breed_japanese_bobtail">Japanese Bobtail</string>
    <string name="descr_japanese_bobtail">This active and affectionate cat will “talk” to you in a
        soft, chirpy voice. You will be amazed by the range of his feline vocabulary. He’s not loud
        at all, but he does have a lot to say and a range of tones in which to say it. When he’s
        not telling you about his day or asking about yours, he is very likely carrying around a
        favorite toy or splashing his paw into your koi pond or aquarium. He likes playing with
        water, so you may find your faucets turned on or puddles beside his water dish.
    </string>

    <string name="breed_serrade_petit">Serrade Petit</string>
    <string name="descr_serrade_petit">Serrade Petit is a cute, little cat that is known for its
        attention seeking nature. It is slightly active and love to indulge in a lot of jumping and
        running around. At the same time, it does not mind lazying around when it feels like.
        Moreover, it is very important that to ensure their proper health, they are allowed to
        exercise a little. Since they love a lot of attention, when the owners participate in a
        variety of activities with them, the cats love all the adoring and undivided attention.
    </string>

    <string name="breed_york_chocolate">York Chocolate</string>
    <string name="descr_york_chocolate">A hardy and athletic farm cat in structure and appearance,
        the York Chocolate is both handsome and distinctive, boasting nimble legs, a heavy carriage,
        wide-spaced, round-tipped ears, bright eyes in green, hazel or amber, a plumed tail and
        semi-longhaired coat. The coat should either be solid chocolate brown, bicolour chocolate
        and white or bicolour chocolate and lilac, darkening as the cat matures from a kitten.
    </string>

    <string name="breed_russian_blue">Russian Blue</string>
    <string name="descr_russian_blue">The Russian Blue has a reputation as a gentle, quiet cat,
        somewhat shy, but don’t get the wrong idea. This cat may have a reserved nature, but he
        loves to play (being especially fond of retrieving) and enjoys jumping or climbing to high
        places where he can study people and situations at his leisure before making up his mind
        about whether he wants to get involved.
    </string>

    <string name="breed_turkish_angora">Turkish Angora</string>
    <string name="descr_turkish_angora">Beautiful and elegant on the surface, the Turkish Angora
        can surprise an unsuspecting owner with his athleticism and intelligence. No bookcase is
        too high for him to reach the top, and no closed door is safe from being opened by his
        questing paws. While he certainly can have lovely manners, the Turkey, as he is sometimes
        nicknamed, has an active, boisterous side to his nature, with a cleverness that makes him
        endlessly entertaining. He likes to play and will do whatever is necessary to get and keep
        your attention, even if it means getting into a little trouble.
    </string>
</resources>

